{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870789718","data":{"timestamp":" 946870789718"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" ef86c3b6-b0fd-4636-8928-8d6e40c6ad33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870789824","data":{"timestamp":" 946870789824"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" ef86c3b6-b0fd-4636-8928-8d6e40c6ad33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870791690","data":{"timestamp":" 946870791690"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" ef86c3b6-b0fd-4636-8928-8d6e40c6ad33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870791832","data":{"timestamp":" 946870791832"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" ef86c3b6-b0fd-4636-8928-8d6e40c6ad33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870797595","data":{"timestamp":" 946870797595"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" ef86c3b6-b0fd-4636-8928-8d6e40c6ad33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870804185","data":{"timestamp":" 946870804184"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" ef86c3b6-b0fd-4636-8928-8d6e40c6ad33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:77..97.off2.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870847654","data":{"timestamp":" 946870847654"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" ef86c3b6-b0fd-4636-8928-8d6e40c6ad33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870857444","data":{"timestamp":" 946870857444"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" ef86c3b6-b0fd-4636-8928-8d6e40c6ad33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870862693","data":{"timestamp":" 946870862693"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" ef86c3b6-b0fd-4636-8928-8d6e40c6ad33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870868872","data":{"timestamp":" 946870868872"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" ef86c3b6-b0fd-4636-8928-8d6e40c6ad33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870884084","data":{"timestamp":" 946870884084"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 02127966-dc56-4154-9580-71b4a38c96a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_53_89-53-57"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 53"," userResponse":" 57"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870891636","data":{"timestamp":" 946870891635"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 02127966-dc56-4154-9580-71b4a38c96a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_53_89-53-57"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 53"," userResponse":" 53"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870896829","data":{"timestamp":" 946870896829"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 02127966-dc56-4154-9580-71b4a38c96a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_95_49-68-95"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 95"," userResponse":" 68"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870903976","data":{"timestamp":" 946870903976"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 02127966-dc56-4154-9580-71b4a38c96a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_95_49-68-95"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 95"," userResponse":" 95"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870910007","data":{"timestamp":" 946870910007"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 02127966-dc56-4154-9580-71b4a38c96a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_97_96-97-92"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 97"," userResponse":" 92"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870917449","data":{"timestamp":" 946870917448"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 02127966-dc56-4154-9580-71b4a38c96a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_97_96-97-92"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 97"," userResponse":" 96"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870929578","data":{"timestamp":" 946870929577"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 02127966-dc56-4154-9580-71b4a38c96a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_97_96-97-92"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870936863","data":{"timestamp":" 946870936863"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 02127966-dc56-4154-9580-71b4a38c96a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_97_96-97-92"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870941652","data":{"timestamp":" 946870941652"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 02127966-dc56-4154-9580-71b4a38c96a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_97_96-97-92"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870948025","data":{"timestamp":" 946870948025"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 02127966-dc56-4154-9580-71b4a38c96a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_97_96-97-92"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870959165","data":{"timestamp":" 946870959165"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" a6f54092-215d-4bf1-be6f-fcfc4924e2c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_82_82-50-55"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 82"," userResponse":" 55"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870966570","data":{"timestamp":" 946870966570"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" a6f54092-215d-4bf1-be6f-fcfc4924e2c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_82_82-50-55"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 82"," userResponse":" 82"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870973502","data":{"timestamp":" 946870973502"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" a6f54092-215d-4bf1-be6f-fcfc4924e2c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_71_83-107-71"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 71"," userResponse":" 71"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870979614","data":{"timestamp":" 946870979614"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" a6f54092-215d-4bf1-be6f-fcfc4924e2c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_95_89-107-95"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 95"," userResponse":" 95"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870990130","data":{"timestamp":" 946870990130"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" a6f54092-215d-4bf1-be6f-fcfc4924e2c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_93_74-83-93"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 93"," userResponse":" 93"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870996861","data":{"timestamp":" 946870996861"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" a6f54092-215d-4bf1-be6f-fcfc4924e2c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_44_49-44-79"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 44"," userResponse":" 49"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871005385","data":{"timestamp":" 946871005384"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" a6f54092-215d-4bf1-be6f-fcfc4924e2c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_44_49-44-79"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 44"," userResponse":" 44"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871009472","data":{"timestamp":" 946871009471"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" a6f54092-215d-4bf1-be6f-fcfc4924e2c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_44_49-44-79"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871046710","data":{"timestamp":" 946871046710"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" aa0ffd49-c12e-4ae0-89f9-16a90a50375e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871048313","data":{"timestamp":" 946871048313"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" aa0ffd49-c12e-4ae0-89f9-16a90a50375e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871056216","data":{"timestamp":" 946871056216"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" aa0ffd49-c12e-4ae0-89f9-16a90a50375e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871056313","data":{"timestamp":" 946871056313"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" aa0ffd49-c12e-4ae0-89f9-16a90a50375e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871097965","data":{"timestamp":" 946871097965"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 6d1ffa51-a0ab-4327-8cf4-3fd14afed36e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871098191","data":{"timestamp":" 946871098191"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 6d1ffa51-a0ab-4327-8cf4-3fd14afed36e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871099154","data":{"timestamp":" 946871099154"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 6d1ffa51-a0ab-4327-8cf4-3fd14afed36e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871100427","data":{"timestamp":" 946871100427"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 6d1ffa51-a0ab-4327-8cf4-3fd14afed36e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871103264","data":{"timestamp":" 946871103264"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 6d1ffa51-a0ab-4327-8cf4-3fd14afed36e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871104108","data":{"timestamp":" 946871104107"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 6d1ffa51-a0ab-4327-8cf4-3fd14afed36e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871104422","data":{"timestamp":" 946871104422"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 6d1ffa51-a0ab-4327-8cf4-3fd14afed36e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871105654","data":{"timestamp":" 946871105654"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 6d1ffa51-a0ab-4327-8cf4-3fd14afed36e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871109161","data":{"timestamp":" 946871109161"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 6d1ffa51-a0ab-4327-8cf4-3fd14afed36e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871110146","data":{"timestamp":" 946871110145"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 6d1ffa51-a0ab-4327-8cf4-3fd14afed36e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871110399","data":{"timestamp":" 946871110399"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 6d1ffa51-a0ab-4327-8cf4-3fd14afed36e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871111343","data":{"timestamp":" 946871111343"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 6d1ffa51-a0ab-4327-8cf4-3fd14afed36e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871114287","data":{"timestamp":" 946871114287"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 6d1ffa51-a0ab-4327-8cf4-3fd14afed36e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871115325","data":{"timestamp":" 946871115324"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 6d1ffa51-a0ab-4327-8cf4-3fd14afed36e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871115804","data":{"timestamp":" 946871115803"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 6d1ffa51-a0ab-4327-8cf4-3fd14afed36e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871117082","data":{"timestamp":" 946871117082"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 6d1ffa51-a0ab-4327-8cf4-3fd14afed36e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956420849","data":{"timestamp":" 946956420849"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956421071","data":{"timestamp":" 946956421071"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956422034","data":{"timestamp":" 946956422034"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956423306","data":{"timestamp":" 946956423306"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956426146","data":{"timestamp":" 946956426146"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956426989","data":{"timestamp":" 946956426989"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956427301","data":{"timestamp":" 946956427301"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956428536","data":{"timestamp":" 946956428536"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956432061","data":{"timestamp":" 946956432061"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956433044","data":{"timestamp":" 946956433044"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956433300","data":{"timestamp":" 946956433300"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956434243","data":{"timestamp":" 946956434243"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956437064","data":{"timestamp":" 946956437063"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956438110","data":{"timestamp":" 946956438110"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956438598","data":{"timestamp":" 946956438598"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956443212","data":{"timestamp":" 946956443211"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956443307","data":{"timestamp":" 946956443307"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956450488","data":{"timestamp":" 946956450488"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" afa949ac-3347-400f-960a-657f17a3828d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956483836","data":{"timestamp":" 946956483836"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_73_73-106-70"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 73"," userResponse":" 73"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956516350","data":{"timestamp":" 946956516349"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_95_89-107-95"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 95"," userResponse":" 89"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956524408","data":{"timestamp":" 946956524408"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_95_89-107-95"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 95"," userResponse":" 95"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956543873","data":{"timestamp":" 946956543873"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_95_49-68-95"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 95"," userResponse":" 95"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956555656","data":{"timestamp":" 946956555656"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_50_104-50-93"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 50"," userResponse":" 93"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956564066","data":{"timestamp":" 946956564066"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_50_104-50-93"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 50"," userResponse":" 50"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956580386","data":{"timestamp":" 946956580385"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_66_66-60-86"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 66"," userResponse":" 86"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956587830","data":{"timestamp":" 946956587830"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_66_66-60-86"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 66"," userResponse":" 66"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956599614","data":{"timestamp":" 946956599614"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_70_48-97-70"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 70"," userResponse":" 70"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956615708","data":{"timestamp":" 946956615708"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_56_56-43-55"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 56"," userResponse":" 55"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956622918","data":{"timestamp":" 946956622918"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_56_56-43-55"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 56"," userResponse":" 56"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956660156","data":{"timestamp":" 946956660156"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_92_90-92-95"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 92"," userResponse":" 95"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956715254","data":{"timestamp":" 946956715254"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_92_90-92-95"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 92"," userResponse":" 92"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956738178","data":{"timestamp":" 946956738178"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_53_89-53-57"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 53"," userResponse":" 53"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956752939","data":{"timestamp":" 946956752939"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_103_88-108-103"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 103"," userResponse":" 103"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956761575","data":{"timestamp":" 946956761574"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_103_88-108-103"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956775533","data":{"timestamp":" 946956775532"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_103_88-108-103"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956783703","data":{"timestamp":" 946956783703"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 503ad633-a439-4d31-9569-83cb0b333ede"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_103_88-108-103"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956816795","data":{"timestamp":" 946956816795"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" fb0221f2-7b03-4ac4-8e12-a53faadd7035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_103_88-108-103"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 103"," userResponse":" 103"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956826704","data":{"timestamp":" 946956826704"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" fb0221f2-7b03-4ac4-8e12-a53faadd7035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_70_48-97-70"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 70"," userResponse":" 70"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956849223","data":{"timestamp":" 946956849223"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" fb0221f2-7b03-4ac4-8e12-a53faadd7035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_71_90-77-71"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 71"," userResponse":" 71"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956863460","data":{"timestamp":" 946956863459"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" fb0221f2-7b03-4ac4-8e12-a53faadd7035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_65_81-65-70"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 65"," userResponse":" 65"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956886115","data":{"timestamp":" 946956886115"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" fb0221f2-7b03-4ac4-8e12-a53faadd7035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_73_73-106-70"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 73"," userResponse":" 73"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956908941","data":{"timestamp":" 946956908941"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" fb0221f2-7b03-4ac4-8e12-a53faadd7035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_95_49-68-95"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 95"," userResponse":" 95"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956917621","data":{"timestamp":" 946956917621"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" fb0221f2-7b03-4ac4-8e12-a53faadd7035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_50_104-50-93"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 50"," userResponse":" 50"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956954592","data":{"timestamp":" 946956954592"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" fb0221f2-7b03-4ac4-8e12-a53faadd7035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_59_89-59-62"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 59"," userResponse":" 62"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956969655","data":{"timestamp":" 946956969655"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" fb0221f2-7b03-4ac4-8e12-a53faadd7035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_59_89-59-62"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 59"," userResponse":" 59"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956975948","data":{"timestamp":" 946956975948"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" fb0221f2-7b03-4ac4-8e12-a53faadd7035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_99_46-99-94"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 99"," userResponse":" 46"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956983126","data":{"timestamp":" 946956983126"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" fb0221f2-7b03-4ac4-8e12-a53faadd7035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_99_46-99-94"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 99"," userResponse":" 94"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956990762","data":{"timestamp":" 946956990762"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" fb0221f2-7b03-4ac4-8e12-a53faadd7035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_99_46-99-94"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 99"," userResponse":" 99"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957012174","data":{"timestamp":" 946957012174"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" fb0221f2-7b03-4ac4-8e12-a53faadd7035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_90_90-43-87"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 90"," userResponse":" 90"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957019020","data":{"timestamp":" 946957019020"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" fb0221f2-7b03-4ac4-8e12-a53faadd7035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_90_90-43-87"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957071884","data":{"timestamp":" 946957071884"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_82_82-50-55"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 82"," userResponse":" 82"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957167411","data":{"timestamp":" 946957167411"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_54_56-82-54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 54"," userResponse":" 82"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957175216","data":{"timestamp":" 946957175216"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_54_56-82-54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 54"," userResponse":" 56"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957182480","data":{"timestamp":" 946957182480"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_54_56-82-54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 54"," userResponse":" 54"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957207541","data":{"timestamp":" 946957207540"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_98_75-98-51"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 98"," userResponse":" 98"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957228378","data":{"timestamp":" 946957228378"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_66_66-60-86"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 66"," userResponse":" 66"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957243727","data":{"timestamp":" 946957243726"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_65_65-97-55"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 65"," userResponse":" 65"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957254747","data":{"timestamp":" 946957254746"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_98_98-83-54"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 98"," userResponse":" 98"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957275777","data":{"timestamp":" 946957275777"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_71_90-77-71"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 71"," userResponse":" 71"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957304756","data":{"timestamp":" 946957304756"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_44_49-44-79"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 44"," userResponse":" 49"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957312767","data":{"timestamp":" 946957312767"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_44_49-44-79"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 44"," userResponse":" 44"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957332275","data":{"timestamp":" 946957332275"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_95_49-68-95"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 95"," userResponse":" 49"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957340092","data":{"timestamp":" 946957340092"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_95_49-68-95"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 95"," userResponse":" 68"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957348226","data":{"timestamp":" 946957348226"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_95_49-68-95"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 95"," userResponse":" 95"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957360501","data":{"timestamp":" 946957360501"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_70_48-97-70"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 70"," userResponse":" 48"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957368867","data":{"timestamp":" 946957368867"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_70_48-97-70"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 70"," userResponse":" 97"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957378019","data":{"timestamp":" 946957378019"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_70_48-97-70"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 70"," userResponse":" 70"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957384953","data":{"timestamp":" 946957384953"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000103_063924"," gameId":" 41ddd57d-a2dc-4c7a-b518-ef8180cca9f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_70_48-97-70"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}